[{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980237039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":16980,"timeElapsed":46978},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980247519,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":10478,"timeElapsed":57459},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980252422,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4901,"timeElapsed":62362},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980255478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3055,"timeElapsed":65418},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980259446,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3966,"timeElapsed":69386},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980267165,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":7717,"timeElapsed":77105},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980271006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":3839,"timeElapsed":80946},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980275046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4038,"timeElapsed":84986},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980277694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"81","question":"In general, do you wish people were MORE or LESS serious? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":2646,"timeElapsed":87634},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980293679,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":15039,"timeElapsed":103618},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980296015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2335,"timeElapsed":105955},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980301367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":5350,"timeElapsed":111306},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980303638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2269,"timeElapsed":113578},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980309478,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5839,"timeElapsed":119418},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980314142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4663,"timeElapsed":124082},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980315901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":1758,"timeElapsed":125841},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980318415,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2512,"timeElapsed":128354},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980320375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1958,"timeElapsed":130314},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980327125,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":5478,"timeElapsed":137065},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980328791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":1664,"timeElapsed":138730},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980332053,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3261,"timeElapsed":141993},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980334974,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2920,"timeElapsed":144914},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980338326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":3350,"timeElapsed":148266},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980344167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":5839,"timeElapsed":154107},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980348126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":3958,"timeElapsed":158066},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980351406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3278,"timeElapsed":161346},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980354166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"42","question":"What is your favorite trait about yourself and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":164106},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980374054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":18773,"timeElapsed":183994},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980376799,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2744,"timeElapsed":186739},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":5973,"timeElapsed":192714},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3239,"timeElapsed":195954},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980387686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1671,"timeElapsed":197626},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980390511,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2823,"timeElapsed":200450},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980392582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2069,"timeElapsed":202522},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980395878,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3295,"timeElapsed":205818},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980404751,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8871,"timeElapsed":214690},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980408054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"97","question":"What is the first thing you hope people notice about you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3302,"timeElapsed":217994},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980415063,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":6111,"timeElapsed":225002},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980417438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2374,"timeElapsed":227378},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980419582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2142,"timeElapsed":229522},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980421662,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":2079,"timeElapsed":231602},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":2886,"timeElapsed":234490},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980427215,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2663,"timeElapsed":237155},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980429374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2158,"timeElapsed":239314},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980431926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":2551,"timeElapsed":241866},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980433390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"159","question":"What is the best book you have read or started in the last three months? Describe it.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1462,"timeElapsed":243330},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980439078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4741,"timeElapsed":249018},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980442726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3647,"timeElapsed":252666},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980445406,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":2679,"timeElapsed":255346},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3574,"timeElapsed":258922},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980450726,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1743,"timeElapsed":260666},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980458246,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":7519,"timeElapsed":268186},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980461262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":3015,"timeElapsed":271202},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464710,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":3446,"timeElapsed":274650},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"25","question":"Complete this sentence: I wish I had someone with whom I could share…","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":2342,"timeElapsed":276994},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980474574,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":6598,"timeElapsed":284514},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980476687,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2111,"timeElapsed":286627},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980479430,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2742,"timeElapsed":289370},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980481222,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1791,"timeElapsed":291162},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980483735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2510,"timeElapsed":293674},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980486182,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2446,"timeElapsed":296122},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980487870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1687,"timeElapsed":297810},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980490031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2159,"timeElapsed":299971},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980491286,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1254,"timeElapsed":301226},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498638,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":6118,"timeElapsed":308578},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980500334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":1694,"timeElapsed":310274},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980502734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":2399,"timeElapsed":312674},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980505454,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2718,"timeElapsed":315394},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980508606,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3150,"timeElapsed":318546},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980511486,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":2879,"timeElapsed":321426},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980514166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2679,"timeElapsed":324106},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980516575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2407,"timeElapsed":326515},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980519622,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3046,"timeElapsed":329562},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980525943,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"182","question":"Who was the first friend you made? How did you become friends? Are you still in touch with them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6319,"timeElapsed":335882},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980533551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":6855,"timeElapsed":343491},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980534767,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1215,"timeElapsed":344706},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980537750,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2982,"timeElapsed":347690},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539806,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2055,"timeElapsed":349746},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980543327,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3519,"timeElapsed":353266},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980547326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3999,"timeElapsed":357266},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548807,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":1479,"timeElapsed":358747},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980551086,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2278,"timeElapsed":361026},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552375,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"141","question":"What is the best restaurant you have been to in the last month? Describe your experience.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":1287,"timeElapsed":362315},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557869,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4686,"timeElapsed":367809},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980561462,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3592,"timeElapsed":371402},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980564397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2934,"timeElapsed":374337},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980566558,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2160,"timeElapsed":376498},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980568358,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":1799,"timeElapsed":378298},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570735,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":2374,"timeElapsed":380675},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980572014,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":1277,"timeElapsed":381953},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980574663,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":2648,"timeElapsed":384603},{"subjectID":"ukhefzue9u","prolificID":"66446d88662725412dc27d06","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b2583234b54b63decad5","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980576575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"14","question":"Is there something that you’ve dreamed of doing for a long time? Why haven’t you done it?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":1910,"timeElapsed":386515}]